{
    "subject": "resource/Septembers_of_Shiraz",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Alon_Aboutboul",
    "human_readable": "The movie Septembers of Shiraz stars Alon Aboutboul.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9224608540534973,
            "question": "Has Alon Aboutboul won any awards for his role in Septembers of Shiraz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8900499939918518,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie Septembers of Shiraz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8401408195495605,
            "question": "Name a movie that features Alon Aboutboul."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.835222065448761,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Alon Aboutboul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7932207584381104,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Septembers of Shiraz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7115265727043152,
            "question": "Is Alon Aboutboul an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.688429057598114,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Septembers of Shiraz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593864560127258,
            "question": "Are there any other movies starring Alon Aboutboul that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6590298414230347,
            "question": "When was the movie Septembers of Shiraz released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.614787757396698,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Septembers of Shiraz likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movie Septembers of Shiraz stars Alon Aboutboul.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4497_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the movie Septembers of Shiraz released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4497_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other movies starring Alon Aboutboul that you know of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4497_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Septembers of Shiraz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4497_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4497_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Alon Aboutboul is indeed a star in the movie Septembers of Shiraz, as mentioned in multiple files (e.g., file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4497/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt and file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4497/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the cast of the film \"Septembers of Shiraz\" includes actors such as Alon Aboutboul. Therefore, the statement that the movie \"Septembers of Shiraz\" stars Alon Aboutboul is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}